const theme_Questions_ProductInfo = [
  [
    { id: 1, title: "Washing instructions" },
    {
      id: 2,
      idTitle: 1,
      question: "How do I care for my running shoes?",
      answer:
        "If your shoes need a good cleaning, first and foremost, do not put them in a washing machine! To clean your On shoes, brush any dirt or debris off. For washing them, wash them by hand only using warm water. It is best to wash your shoes as seldom as possible. Go here for more specific instructions.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 3, title: "Limited editions" },
    {
      id: 4,
      idTitle: 3,
      question: "Can I return limited edition?",
      answer:
        "Yes, you can return all On purchases for a refund if the items are in eligible condition, in their original intact packaging, and within the 30-day return window. These items are not exchangeable.",
    },

    {
      id: 5,
      idTitle: 3,
      question: "Can I exchange limited edition?",
      answer:
        "We are unable to exchange Limited Edition or Last Season items due to limited inventory, but they can be refunded if eligible. Certain THE ROGER Line products can be exchanged, but not all. When you submit your return or exchange request, it will not give you the option to exchange if the item is not exchangeable.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 6, title: "Shoe advice" },
    {
      id: 7,
      idTitle: 6,
      question: "How long a pair of On Shoe usally last?",
      answer:
        "It depends on many factors, such as running style, weight, and the surface you run on. But generally, shoes (not just On shoes) last up to 300 miles (approx. 482 km) depending on the model and materials used. For example, some of our styles, such as the Cloudboom Echo, are designed for high-performance racing, so naturally, they won't have the same durability as an all-day shoe like the Cloud 5.",
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      idTitle: 6,
      question: "What terrain or weather conditions can On Shoes be used in?",
      answer:
        "On comes from Switzerland, so our products have been tested throughout different seasons and landscapes. We have Performance Running shoes for running city streets wherever you may be, and our Performance Outdoor collection will support you when you hit the trails. For On Apparel, each product's page indicates weather-resistant, water-resistant, or weatherproof.",
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      idTitle: 6,
      question: "Can On Running shoes be used for walkiing?",
      answer:
        "While On Performance Running shoes were designed specifically for running purposes, they are excellent for all-day comfort and can be used for walking, exploring, or mixed workouts. You can chat with the Happiness Delivery Team by visiting our Contact Us form to ask for advice about which shoe is the best for your needs!",
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      idTitle: 6,
      question: "How do I know which size I need?",
      answer:
        "If you're unsure which size you wear in our footwear or apparel, each product page has a size chart and fit recommendation. For Performance Running and Performance Outdoor models, the standard recommendation is one size bigger than your everyday shoe size. The Japanese sizing is in centimeters, so you can also measure your foot by standing barefoot with your heel against a wall, adding about 1 cm to your measured size for an indication of what size will work for you.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 11, title: "Laces and insoles" },
    {
      id: 12,
      idTitle: 11,
      question:
        "What is On's unique speed lace system found in our cloudy family shoes?",
      answer:
        "On's Cloud family includes the Cloud 5, Cloud 5 Waterproof, Cloud 5 Terry, Cloud 5 Push, Cloud 5 Fuse, Cloud 5 Combo, and Cloud 5 Coast. They all feature our signature speed lacing system. We want to help you slip on your shoes or flick them off with ease. These models were specially designed to support speed lacing so it won't work with our other shoes. If you need to adjust for a tighter fit, you can retie the knots at the ends for a more snug fit. Most Cloud 5 family shoes come with an additional pair of conventional laces in the box so you can decide how you want the shoe to work for you, but not all models in this family do.",
    },
    {
      id: 13,
      idTitle: 11,
      question: "How can I get replacements laces?",
      answer:
        "If you are in need of a new set of laces, you can ask a Happiness Deliverer for your options via the Contact Us form. Please note, our lace inventory for replacements is very limited as laces are custom installed on each shoe. If you believe the issue is a defect or quality issue, you can also submit a warranty claim here for our warranty specialists to review.",
    },
    {
      id: 14,
      idTitle: 11,
      question: "Will receive an extra pair of laces with my On shoes?",
      answer:
        "We only include a set of extra laces for the Cloud 5 family shoes. The Cloud 5, the Cloud 5 Waterproof, the Cloud 5 Push, the Cloud 5 Combo, the Cloud 5 Fuse, and the Cloud 5 Terry. We do not send extra laces for the Cloud 5 Coast, though. We do this to give customers who prefer conventional laces over speed lacing the option. All of our other models come with just one set of conventional laces, custom installed.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 15, title: "Stock availability" },
    {
      id: 16,
      idTitle: 15,
      question: "What do I do if the item I want is out of stock in my size?",
      answer:
        "Our website only allows you to order something in stock and available on our webshop. If we do not have stock of the product you've got your eyes on, you can click the item and enter your email when prompted. If the item is coming back, you will be prompted to sign up for stock updates. If we do not have plans to restock, you will be prompted to sign up for the newsletter.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 17, title: "Manufacturing" },
    {
      id: 18,
      idTitle: 17,
      question: "Where are On shoes made?",
      answer:
        "We've traveled the world to find the best partners to produce every On item. Meet them all and learn more about how On items are produced here.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 19, title: "Produc feedback " },
    {
      id: 20,
      idTitle: 19,
      question: "Where can submit feedback about On products",
      answer:
        "We'd love to hear your feedback! You can let us know about your experience with your On gear by speaking to a Happiness Deliverer via our Contact Us form or reaching out to our socials.",
    },
  ],
  [
    { id: 20, title: "Warranty claims " },
    {
      id: 21,
      idTitle: 20,
      question: "How do I know if I have a warranty issue?",
      answer:
        "If you're experiencing an issue with an On product that seems irregular, submit a Warranty claim! We handle claims on a case-by-case basis, so once you submit, we'll get back to you to let you know if your product is eligible for a warranty.",
    },
    {
      id: 22,
      idTitle: 20,
      question: "How can I submit warranty claims?",
      answer:
        "Simply go to our Warranty claim form, provide details and images of the issue, and we'll get back to you with the result. Please note that a claim can only be made for purchases from On directly (or from authorized retailers) and requires proof of purchase.",
    },
  ],
];

export default theme_Questions_ProductInfo;
